How to make an umbrella
To make an umbrella, open the previous umbrella
Then delete the excess panels
Then use the edit panel tool to measure the total length of the entire waist panel
In the attribute editor on the right, we can see
The length of the symmetrical correction is the total length of two lines
Then we use the create circle tool to create a circle panel
The circle circle length is the total length we just measured
Then double click on a line
We can select the whole line
Then right-click to select the panel outline expansion
The length of the expansion here is the length of the skirt at the end
Remember to choose the depth line after the expansion
Otherwise there is no middle line
We can't dig the inner line
After the depth line
Double click on an inner line
Select the entire inner line
Then switch to move
This part of the hollow in the middle
We will sew on the waist in a moment
To make it easier to sew
We choose the free sewing tool here
Then press the Shift key
Start from the front
Because it is from left to right
So when we turn to the other side
Also click from left to right
Then arrange this panel in 3D space
Be careful when arranging the sewing line
Don't cross
After opening the model
You can see that the entire umbrella is worn on the model
Because the length of our waist is equal
So it's flat here on the waist
There are no wrinkles here
The wrinkles are formed below
Because the skirt is very large
In fact, it's a bit similar to the front and back skirt we made before
It's just that the front and back skirt is part of it
Then we made a whole circle
Reduce the thickness of the particle joint and the bulge
Make it more smooth to simulate
Because the structure of the umbrella skirt is special
It is a round version
Its direction of texture is actually changing in all directions
So we
If you want to adjust its physical properties
Try to ensure that its value is equal
Is the same as the value of the gold and silver tail
In addition
We can also apply a pressure to the fabric
This pressure
We have to click the left arrow to enter 0.5
Don't add too much
When we give it a value of 0.5
Or a smaller value
We can see this umbrella skirt
Because of its own weight
And the balance of pressure
It looks a little bumpy
Because it is more stable
and the front and back skirt is already the same
Let's make it a little more smooth
To make it more natural
Give it a little more pressure
Let's do it again
If we want to change its physical properties
For example, we modified the bending intensity
If you want to make it look a little bit harder
Then we
Gold tail
Even the bending intensity of the oblique is as much as a value
If you want to add a pleats of the umbrella skirt
First of all, you can enlarge the entire version
If you feel that the skirt has been changed too much, you can use the narrowing function to shorten the skirt.
After completion, you can save the file.